

Yuta Yanagisawa

Full-Stack Web Developer



Summary

Adaptable professional web developer with 2.5+ years of experience and a proven knowledge of web application development, website architecture, and web platform development. Designed and developed over 10 advanced web applications both backend side and frontend side from use cases and functional requirements with different frameworks and language (mainly Java). Seeking to leverage my technical and professional experience and expertise to provide impact to the team and grow more as a developer.



Experience

2016-05 -2017-02

Web developer

Yume Technology Inc.

- Provides design development of projects involving application development, migrations, and additions to existing applications.
- Developed up to 3 static web pages using php.

2017-04 - present

Full-Stack Web Developer

Soliton Systems K.K.

- Designed and developed up to 5 applications projects per year
 - mostly company information management application server
 - Web Shop (Backend)
 - Mobile App (Mailer and Task Manager)
 - Application Middlewares
 - Secure API Server
- Designed project requirements in cooperation with end users
- Agile Software Development as a Team using Github Development Flow (70% coding, 30% code review)
- Monitor every project and fix in time whenever abnormalities appear
- Participated in project meetings, with technical staff members, end users
- Trained and mentored 2 entry programmers and developer

Tech stack:

- Mainly Java for server side and client side using Play Framework
- Kotlin (Spring boot)
- React, Angular (FrontEnd)
- Golang (for Backend only projects)
- PostgreSQL
- Docker
- Jenkins (Deployment)
- Kibana, Grafana (app monitoring)



Education

2011-06 -2016-05

Bulacan State University, Philippines, BS in Computer Engineering, 2016

- National Quiz Bee Competition contestant and finalist for 2 years
- Regional Quiz bee Competition champion for 3 Years
- Consistent Top 1 student in Class and Graduated Top 6 student in overall



Phone

(given upon request)

E-mail

yutayandc@gmail.com

Date of birth

1994-07-03

GitHub

https://github.com/TechYuts

My Website

https://www.yuts.me/

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/yutayandc/



Java

••••

Git

Javascript

Typescript

React

PostgreSQL

Angular

Kotlin

Kibana

Jenkins

Docker



Japanese



English



Tagalog

